Grove Press Records
Grove Press Records
- Books - Book files (by author)
  - Hennessey, Sharon [pseudonym: Octavia Natoma]
    - With Tongue in Cheek
      - Project file, 1973; photographs of author, correspondence, including letter from Freude Bartlett/Serious Business Company (Box 340)
  - Henriques, Fernando
    - Prostitution and Society
      - Contract, rights, 1965-1966 (Box 340)
      - Project file, 1962; 1965,; 1967; clippings, correspondence, proposal (Box 340)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1966 (Box 340)
      - Royalties, Citadel (Z-1003), 1965-1970 (Box 340)
  - Henry, Will
    - Marital Spanking
      - Contract, 1972 (Box 340)
    - Modern Bondage
      - Contract, 1972 (Box 340)
    - Whipping Girls
      - Contract, 1972 (Box 340)
  - Hentoff, Nat
    - Correspondence, author, 1956-1960; 1968-1971 (Box 340)
    - A Doctor Among Addicts
      - Contract, 1970; 1975 (Box 340)
      - Production, Camera copy, 2 folders (Box 340)
      - Production, Corrected copy (Box 340)
      - Project file, 1969-1971; correspondence, jackets (including Rand McNally edition), jacket copy, etc. (Box 340)
      - Royalties (B-267), 1970 (Box 341)
    - Jazz
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1960-1961 (Box 341)
      - Project file, 1959-1960; correspondence, jacket from Rinehart edition, proposal, production notes (Box 341)
      - Royalties (E-277), 1960-1964; 1970 (Box 341)
    - The Jazz Makers
      - Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 341)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1958 (Box 341)
      - Rights and permissions, 1971 (Box 341)
      - Royalties (E-125), 1958-1963 (Box 341)
  - Herbert, Edward
    - A Confucian Notebook, part of the Wisdom of the East series
      - Production, Camera copy (Box 341)
      - Project file, circa 1960 (Box 341)
      - Royalties, John Murray Ltd., 1961-1963 (Box 341)
    - A Taoist Notebook, part of the Wisdom of the East series
      - Production, Camera copy, marked-up hardcover undidentified edition (Box 341)
      - Project file, circa 1960 (Box 341)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1961 (Box 341)
      - Royalties, John Murray, 1961-1963 (Box 341)
  - Herbert, John
    - Fortune and Men's Eyes
      - Contract, 1967; 1971; indcludes quitclaim (Box 341)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1980 (Box 341)
      - Production, Photographs, 1967; from stage productions (Box 341)
      - Production, Plate proof (Box 341)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 341)
      - Project file, 1967-1968; correspondence, clippings, list of prison slang, issue of Showcard, sheet music for "A Prisoner's Song," etc. (Box 341)
      - Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 341)
      - Rights and permissions, 1968; 1971,; 1983 (Box 342)
      - Royalties (E-457), 1967-1970 (Box 342)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (E-457), 1968-1969 (Box 342)
  - Hermans, Willem
    - The Dark Room of Damocles
      - Contract, royalties, 1960; 1963-1964 (Box 342)
      - Correspondence, 1959-1969; includes Roy Edwards (translator), also a few clippings and manuscript corrections (Box 342)
  - Hernton, Calvin
    - Sex and Racism in America
      - Contract, 1965 (Box 342)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1965-1968; 1975 (Box 342)
      - Correspondence, 1965; 1969-1972 (Box 342)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1970; 1977-1978 (Box 342)
      - Royalties (B-113), 1965-1970 (Box 342)
      - Royalties (B-306), 1971 (Box 342)
  - Hibbett, Howard
    - The Floating World in Japanese Fiction
      - Production, Camera copy, 3 folders (Box 342)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1959-1960 (Box 342)
      - Project file, 1959-1960; proposal, correspondence, production estimates, jacket from Oxford University Press edition (Box 342)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1959-1961 (Box 342)
      - Royalties (E-255), 1960-1964 (Box 342)
  - Higgins, Aidan
    - Correspondence, author, 1959-1966; includes issue of The London Magazine with text of "Balcony of Europe," signed and inscribed by the author to Rossett; 4 folders (Box 342)
    - Correspondence, author, 1967-1969 (Box 343)
    - Balcony of Europe
      - Contract, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 343)
      - Excerpts, 1968-1970; typescript photocopies, some correpondence (Box 343)
      - Project file, 1966-1969; 1972; sample pages, photos for jacket art ideas (Box 343)
      - Royalties, 1966-1971 (Box 343)
    - Killachter Meadow
      - Correspondence, 1959-1961; includes clippings (Box 343)
      - Production, Extra repros, 2 folders (Box 343)
      - Production, Mechanicals, 3 folders (Box 343)
      - Royalties (E-269), 1959-1971 (Box 343)
    - Langrishe, Go Down
      - Photographs, Author, 1967 (Box 343)
      - Production, Edited material, 2 folders (Box 343)
      - Production, Jacket art ideas (photographs), 2 folders (Box 343)
      - Production, Manuscript, includes author's notes to editors; 2 folders (Box 344)
      - Production, Setting copy, disbound hardcover edition, unidentified; 2 folders (Box 344)
      - Project file, 1961-1962; 1965-1968; correspondence, marked-up manuscript pages, clippings, etc. (Box 344)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1966-1967 (Box 345)
      - Publicity, General, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 344)
      - Royalties (GP-384), 1961-1971; includes copy of contract, rights reversion letter (Box 345)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-384), 1967-1969 (Box 345)
  - Hill, Herbert
    - The Abolitionists
      - Contract, 1960-1963; includes one royalty payment, correspondence with author (Box 345)
      - Project file, book outline, reprint of article by Hill (Box 345)
  - Hills, Denis
    - The White Pumpkin
      - Contract, 1975-1978 (Box 345)
      - Correspondence, Author, 1975-1977 (Box 345)
      - Photographs, Author, 1975; numerous prints and negativse (Box 345)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1975-1976 (Box 345)
      - Production, Negatives, 1975 (Box 345)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1975-1977 (Box 345)
      - Publicity, General, 1975-1976 (Box 345)
  - The History of Art
    - Project file, 1961; correspondence, drafts, notes; 2 folders (Box 345)
  - Hitler, Adolf
    - Hitler's Secret Book
      - Correspondence, Telford Taylor, 1961-1962; Telford Taylor (introduction) (Box 345)
      - Production, German manuscript, pp. 1-141; 2 folders (Box 345)
      - Production, German manuscript, pp. 142-324; 2 folders (Box 346)
      - Production, Manuscript, includes introduction by Telford Taylor; 5 folders (Box 346)
      - Production, Photographs, 2 photos of Hitler, multiple copies of one (Box 346)
      - Project file, 1960-1966; 1968; considerable amount of correspondence, also notes, clippings, etc.; 2 folders (Box 346)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1962 (Box 347)
      - Publicity, General, 1962 (Box 347)
      - Rights and permissions, 1964 (Box 347)
      - Royalties, Dieter Lattmann (GP-261), 1961-1965 (Box 347)
      - Royalties, Selfhelp (E-373), 1961-1968 (Box 347)
  - Hittleman, Richard
    - Yoga: 28 Day Exercise Plan
      - Project file, 1970; correspnonence, contract termination (Box 347)
  - Hobson, Harold
    - International Theatre Annual
      - Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 347)
      - Production, Manuscript of introduction by Robert Morley, reproduction of typescript (Box 347)
      - Royalties (E-183), 1959-1966 (Box 347)
  - Hocart, A.M.
    - The Life-Giving Myth
      - Project file, 1953; corrrespondence, jackets from Grove and Methuen editions, typescript blurbs (Box 347)
      - Publicity, 1952-1954; includes studio portrait of author (Box 347)
  - Hochhuth, Rolf
    - Correspondence, author, 1963-1970; includes author photographs (Box 347)
    - The Berline Antigone
      - Production, Misecllaneous, status report; also lists word counts and status of books by McClure, Shapiro, Burroughs, Ionesc, Williams, Gysin, Grass, Genet, Musil, Young, Mailer, and Roche (Box 347)
    - The Deputy
      See also Bentley, Eric: The Storm over "The Deputy"
      - Correspondence, Changes and edits, 1963; includes marked-up typescript pages (Box 347)
      - Correspondence, Preminger libel suit, 1964 (Box 347)
      - Correspondence, Publicity, 1964; includes some with Eric Bentley (Box 347)
      - Correspondence, Review copy requests, 1964 (Box 347)
      - Panel discussions, 1964; correspondence, advertisements (Box 348)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1970; 1976,; 1978 (Box 348)
      - Production, Marked copy, Grove Press hardcover edition (Box 348)
      - Production, Page proofs (Box 348)
      - Production, Photographs, 1963 (Box 348)
      - Production, Setting copy, pp. 1-364; 4 folders (Box 348)
      - Production, Setting copy, pp. 365-434, author afterword; 2 folders (Box 349)
      - Project files, 1963-1972; vast majority is correspondence (Box 349)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1963-1964; includes "Worldwide reaction to The Deputy" with collected comments by Albert Schweitzer, Pope Paul VI, Pastor Niemöller and others (Box 349)
      - Publicity, Ads, 1964 (Box 349)
      - Publicity, Ads and ad proofs, 1964 (Box 350)
      - Publicity, Bannings, 1965; Rome and Brazil (Box 350)
      - Publicity, Best seller lists, 1964 (Box 350)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1963-1964; 5 folders (Box 350)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1963-1967; includes pro and con, best seller lists; 5 folders (Box 351)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1964-1969 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Clippings and interviews, 1963-1964 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Columnists, editorials, 1964 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, The Comforter, 1964 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Foreign clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Literary reviews, 1963-1964 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Melcher award, 1965 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, News clippings, 1964; 1967-1969 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Religious group mailings, 1963-1964 (Box 352)
      - Publicity, Theater clippings, 1964 (Box 353)
      - Publicity, Vatican clippings, 1964 (Box 353)
      - Rights and permissions, 1964-1965 (Box 353)
      - Royalties (B-154), 1967-1970 (Box 353)
      - Royalties (B-1889), 1965-1970 (Box 353)
      - Royalties (GP-312), 1963-1969 (Box 353)
      - Royalties, Book of the month (GP-312), 1964-1969 (Box 353)
      - Royalties, Dell (GP-312), 1964-1965 (Box 353)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-312), 1968-1969 (Box 353)
      - Royalties, Hudson Book Club (HB-312), 1964-1966 (Box 353)
      - Royalties, Mid-Century Book Club (HB-312), 1965 (Box 353)
      - Royalties, Samuel French (GP-312), 1968-1970 (Box 353)
    - Guerillas
      - Project file, 1970; clippings, a little correspnodence (Box 353)
    - Resignation, or, The Story of a Marriage
      - Manuscript in German, with English translation (Box 353)
    - Soldiers
      - Contracts, 1967-1968; includes correspondence, copyright (Box 353)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 354)
      - Essays [?] by Hochhuth, circa 1967 (Box 353)
      - Production, Photographs, 1967; from performance at Freie Volksbühne, Berlin (Box 353)
      - Production, Setting copy, pp. 1-139; 2 folders (Box 353)
      - Production, Setting copy, pp. 140-273 (Box 354)
      - Project file, 1968-1969; correspondence, jacket, clippings, notes, etc. (Box 354)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1968 (Box 354)
      - Publicity, New York Times Magazine, 1967 (Box 354)
      - Publicity, German, 1967; 3 folders (Box 354)
      - Publicity, Toronto, 1968; 2 folders (Box 354)
      - Publicity, Great Britain, 1967 (Box 355)
      - Publicity, Vienna, 1967 (Box 355)
      - Publicity, Other, 1967 (Box 355)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1967-1969; 6 folders (Box 355)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 356)
      - Rights and permissions, 1971; 1983 (Box 356)
      - Royalties (B-200), 1969-1970 (Box 356)
      - Royalties (GP-467), 1967-1970 (Box 356)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-467), 1968-1969 (Box 356)
      - Royalties, Greenburger (French) [empty folder] (Box 356)
  - Ho Chi Minh Project
    - Project file, 1969 (Box 356)
  - Hocquard, Jean-Victor
    - Mozart
      - Project file, 1958; Library of Congress slip only (Box 356)
  - Hodeir, Andre
    - Correspondence, author, 1954-1973; 1977,; 1981; 4 folders (Box 356)
    - Correspondence, Savoy Music Company, 1956-1957; letters from Barney Rosset, acting on Hodeir's behalf (Box 356)
    - Cleopatra Goes Sledding, illustrated by Tomi Ungerer
      - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 356)
      - Production, Layout (Box 356)
      - Production, Manuscript (Box 356)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1967-1968 (Box 356)
      - Publicity, General, 1967-1968 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Hodeir (GP-391), 1965-1970 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Ungerer (GP-391), 1965-1970 (Box 357)
    - Jazz: Its Evolution and Essence
      - Correspondence, Secker and Warburg, 1955-1957; 1965-1967 (Box 357)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1965; 1969,; 1972-1973; includes David Noakes (final translator), Walter Schaap (initial translator), Nat Hentoff (Box 357)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1979-1980 (Box 357)
      - Production, Manuscript, introduction by Martin Williams (Box 357)
      - Project file, 1954-1963; typescripts of introduction, appendix; clippings (Box 357)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1977 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Librairie Flammarion and Hodeir (BC-3), 1954-1956; 1961-1970 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Librairie Flammarion and Hodeir (E-70), 1956-1965 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Noakes (BC-3), 1961-1970 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Noakes (E-70), 1956-1965 (Box 357)
    - Since Debussy
      - Contract, Da Capo Press, 1974 (Box 357)
      - Contract, Microtexts Library, 1971 (Box 357)
      - Correspondence, Noel Burch (translator), 1959-1960 (Box 357)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1969; includes John Ashbery (Box 357)
      - Photographs, Author, circa 1960 (Box 357)
      - Publicity, 1960-1961 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Hodeir (E-260), 1956; 1959-1966 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Nymphenburger Verhandlerung (E-260), 1957; 1960-1962; includes contract (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Presses Universitaires (E-260), 1960-1963 (Box 357)
      - Royalties, Secker and Warburg (E-260), 1961-1969; includes correspondence, contract (Box 357)
    - Toward Jazz
      - Correspondence, Noel Burch (translator), 1960; 1964 (Box 358)
      - Project file, 1961-1964; 1970; correpondence, proposal, notes, manufacturing estimate (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Hodeir (E-383), 1963-1970 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Hodeir (GP-283), 1960-1965 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Jazz Book Club (GP-283), 1964-1965 (Box 358)
    - Warwick's Three Bottles, illustrated by Tomi Ungerer
      - Contract, Diogenes Verlag, 1965-1966; 1974 (Box 358)
      - Correspondence, Tomi Ungerer (Illustrator), 1964-1965 (Box 358)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1971; includes some with French publishers; mention of Cleopatra Goes Sledding (Box 358)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 sets, one edited; 2 folders (Box 358)
      - Production, Artwork, original watercolor illustrations by Tomi Ungerer (Oversize 35)
      - Project file, proposal, reader's report, sketch, clippings, half-titles (Box 358)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1966-1967 (Box 358)
      - Publicity, General, 1966-1967 (Box 358)
      - Rejected art, Jerome Kuhl, circa 1963 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Delpire (GP-370), 1967 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Diogenes Verlag (GP-370), 1966-1970 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-370), 1967-1969 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Hodeir (GP-370), 1965-1970 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Hodeir (GL-370), 1966-1969 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Kodansha Ltd. (GP-370), 1971 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Ungerer (GP-370), 1965-1970 (Box 358)
      - Royalties, Ungerer (GL-370), 1966-1969 (Box 358)
    - The Worlds of Jazz
      - Contract, Gallimard, 1957-1958 (Box 358)
      - Correspondence, David Noakes (translator), 1958-1959 (Box 358)
      - Correspondence, Noel Burch (translator), 1967; 1969 (Box 358)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1970-1972; 1978 (Box 359)
      - Production, Setting copy, 4 folders (Box 359)
      - Project file, 1957-1962; 1969,; 1970; correspondence, photos, editorial notes, clippings, etc. (Box 359)
  - Hodgson, John and Richards, Eugene
    - Improvisation
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1979; estimate only (Box 359)
  - Hoffenberg, Mason, See Southern, Terry: Candy.
  - Hoffman, Abbie
    - Dear Abbie
      - Correspondence, 1970; also discusses Abbie Hoffman in Chicago (Box 359)
      - Hoffman v. Hoffman testimony, 1969 (Box 359)
      - "Dear Abbie" letters, 1969; photocopies only, no originals; includes one from Dr. Benjamin Spock (Box 359)
    - Steal This Book
      - Contract, 1970 (Box 359)
      - Correspondence, 1972; 1974 (Box 359)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1971-1972 (Box 360)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 360)
  - Hoffman, Anita, See Fettamine, Ann.
  - Hoffmann, E.T.A. and Lazare, Christopher (editor)
    - Tales of Hoffmann
      - Correspondence, 1957-1963; includes Christopher Lazare (Box 360)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1958-1959 (Box 360)
      - Publicity, Clippings, 1958-1959 (Box 360)
      - Royalties (E-147), 1958-1963 (Box 360)
  - Hoffman, Frederick J.
    - Freudianism and the Literary Mind
      - Correspndence, author and others, 1958-1959; 1963 (Box 360)
      - Photographs, Author, circa 1958 (Box 360)
      - Royalties (E-168), 1958-1965 (Box 360)
  - Hofmann, Gert
    - Correspondence, Author, 1967 (Box 360)
    - Photographs, Author, 1968 (Box 360)
    - The Burgomaster
      - Contract, copyright, 1964; 1968,; 1971 (Box 360)
      - Correspondence, Donald Watson (translator), 1963-1964; 1967-1968 (Box 360)
      - Production, Galleys, edited (Box 360)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 360)
      - Project file, 1963-1964; 1967-1968; correspondence, notes, jacket, production estimates, etc. (Box 360)
      - Publicity, 1963; 1968 (Box 360)
      - Royalties, Fisher Verlag (E-427), 1964-1970 (Box 360)
      - Royalties, Watson (translator), 1964-1970 (Box 360)
    - The Son, Vacationing in Miami, and Our Man in Madras
      - Project file, 1967; 1970; contract, correspondence (Box 360)
      - Royalties, 1967-1971 (Box 360)
  - Hofmann, Michael R.
    - Tchaikovsky
      - Project file, 1959-1960; correspondence, production notes, set of galleys/proofs (Box 361)
  - Hogg, James
    - The Private Memoirs and Confessions of a Justified Sinner
      - Correspondence, 1958-1959; 1964; includes jacket from Cresset edition (Box 361)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1959 (Box 361)
      - Publicity, 1959 (Box 361)
  - Holder, Maryse
    - Give Sorrow Words
      - Production, Galleys, corrected; 3 folders (Box 361)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1978-1979 (Box 361)
      - Production, Setting copy, 5 folders (Box 361)
  - Holderlin, Friedrich
    - Selected Poems
      - Project file, 1956; 1962; correspondence, jacket from Hogarth Press edition (Box 361)
  - Hollitscher, Walter
    - Psychoanalysis and Civilization: An Introduction to Sigmund Freud
      - Production, Camera copy, disbound and marked-up Oxford edition (Box 362)
      - Production, Marked copy, disbound and marked-up Oxford edition (Box 362)
      - Project file, 1961-1963; correspondence, proposal, art schedule, notes (Box 362)
      - Royalties (E-356), 1962-1969 (Box 362)
  - Hollo, Anselm
    - [untitled poetry collection]
      - Correspondence, author, 1965-1966; 1969 (Box 361)
  - Holm, Sven (editor)
    See also Anderberg, Bengt: Love 1 and Love 2: Erotic Tales from Scandanavia.
    - Love 2: Erotic Tales from Denmark
      - Contract, 1966; 1969,; 1970 (Box 362)
      - Production, Galleys (Box 362)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1969-1970 (Box 362)
      - Production, Setting copy, 3 folders (Box 362)
      - Project file, 1965-1971; correspondence, jacket, ranking of stories, sample translations, etc.; mentions Bengt Anderberg, Love 1 and 2: Erotic tales from Scandinavia (Box 362)
      - Royalties (X-1012), 1970 (Box 362)
      - Royalties, Hans Reitzel Ltd., 1966-1971; includes questions about Love 1 (Box 362)
  - Holt, P.M.
    - A Modern History of the Sudan
      - Correspondence, 1961-1962; includes letter from Chester Bowles, undersecretary of state, praising book; list of proposed titles for Grove's Asia-Africa series (Box 363)
      - Royalties (HB-256), 1961-1963 (Box 363)
  - Holthusen, Hans Egon
    - Rainer Maria Rilke
      - Contract, 1960 (Box 363)
      - Project file, 1959-1963; correspondence, reader's reports, Rilke biographical information, lists, editorial notes, etc. (Box 363)
      - Royalties, 1960; 1963,; 1965 (Box 363)
  - Honig, Albert
    - Home Treatment of Mental Illness
      - Project file, 1965-1966; author correspondence, book outline, clippings, reprints of articles by Honig (Box 363)
  - Hook, Sidney
    - Psychoanalysis, Scientific Method and Philosophy
      - Correspondence, 1959-1961; 1969; includes production estimate (Box 363)
      - Photograph, Author, 1959 (Box 363)
      - Royalties (E-261), 1959-1966 (Box 363)
  - Hopkins, Jeffrey, See Sopa, Geshe and Hopkins, Jeffrey.
  - Horn, Richard
    - Correspondence, author, 1967-1971 (Box 363)
    - Encyclopedia [novel]
      - Contract, 1968 (Box 363)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 363)
      - Project file, 1968-1971; correspondence, jacket, reader's report, production/editorial notes, etc. (Box 363)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1969 (Box 363)
      - Publicity, General, 1969 (Box 363)
      - Royalties (GP-505), 1968-1970 (Box 363)
    - [untitled "Super magical pornographic Indian travelogue"]
      - Project file, 1968; outline, contract, check request (Box 363)
      - Royalties, 1968-1971 (Box 363)
  - Hornwood, Harvey, See also Danziger, David [pseudonym].
    - The Hard Life
      - Project file, 1972-1973; author correspondence, contracts (Box 363)
    - Lenny (novelization), See Barry, Julian: Lenny.
  - Hortelano, Juan Garcia
    - Summer Storm
      - Correspondence, author, 1965 (Box 364)
      - Project file, 1961-1965; 1990; mostly correspondence; includes translator Ilsa Bareo, jackets from other publishers' editions, publicity relating to Prix Formentor, reader reports, proposal, copyright (Box 364)
      - Rights and permissions, 1968-1969 (Box 364)
      - Royalties (BC-57), 1961-1966 (Box 364)
      - Royalties (GP-267), 1961-1965 (Box 364)
  - Horton, Philip
    - Hart Crane
      - Correspondence, 1955; Norman Holmes Pearson, Brom Weber (Box 364)
  - Houghton, Norris
    - Moscow Rehearsals
      - Production, Camera copy, disbound Harcourt Brace edition; 4 folders (Box 364)
      - Project file, 1961-1964; correspondence, production estimates (Box 364)
      - Royalties (E-343), 1962-1966 (Box 364)
  - Houston, Jean, See Masters, Robert E.L.: Psychedelic Art.
  - Howard, Lisa, See Weiner, Sue and Howard, Lisa: Rolling Stones A-Z.
  - Howard, Munroe
    - Call Me Brick [original title: Mortar and Pestle]
      - Correspondence, Author, 1965-1973 (Box 364)
      - Correspondence, General, 1967-1969; includes press release, reader's report, mention of Howard's Run Sheep Run (Box 364)
      - Photograph, Author, circa 1967 (Box 364)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 364)
      - Publicity, 1967-1969 (Box 365)
      - Royalties (GP-411), 1966-1970 (Box 365)
      - Royalties, Agence Hoffman (GP-411), 1969; 1971 (Box 365)
      - Royalties, Alexander Gans (GP-411), 1969-1971 (Box 365)
      - Royalties, Dais (GP-411), 1969; 1971 (Box 365)
      - Royalties, Dell (GP-411), 1968-1971 (Box 365)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club, 1967-1970 (Box 365)
  - Howard, Richard